DOMINIC EFEOGHENE ADJEH

Lagos, Nigeria · +2348158389029 · dominicadjeh@gmail.com

SUMMARY

A detail-oriented organized and inquisitive student. Performed excellently and worked closely with several teams towards established goals. Contributed to team exercises, performed with merit and contributed my quota to the attainment of corporate vision having acquired relevant Project management and Programming knowledge.

EDUCATION

November 2020 – Present

400L Computer Engineering. CGPA: 4.91/5.00 (B.Eng. 1st class Hons in-view). Elizade University, Ilara Mokin Ondo State.

• 2019

SSCE Certificate King's College, Lagos.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Trainee

Julius Berger Head Office,

IT Department, Port Harcourt.

(April 2023 – Present)

- CCTV Installation.
- Developed a restful API for Mobile and Web applications using Django rest frameworks.
- Designed a To-do List Web Application equipped with user authentication and privacy using Django.
- Designed a Notes Web application using Django and React.

Fullstack Developer

HIIT PLC Ikeja, Lagos.

(August 2023 – November 2023)

- Completed a certification course in Frontend development (HTML CSS and JavaScript)
- Completed a certification course in Backend Development using Django Framework
- Designed an E-Commerce Web Application using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python (Django)

Graphics Designer

Gibraltar Technologies

(August 2021 – October 2021)

- Completed final touches for projects such as images sizes and font selection
 Observed how edits were made on recorded videos obtained from event coverage
- · Conducted interviews with clients.
- Took pictures of events to be supplied to the graphic designers.
- Assisted the Newsletter and Magazine department in updating newsletters.

SKILLS

skills: Python Programming | Sales | Microsoft Office Suite | Frontend Web development | Rest API Development | Mobile App design |

interests: Product Development | Gaming | Economics

ACHIEVEMENTS AND AWARDS

- **★ Recognition of Brilliant Academic Performance** (December 2022) Elizade University, Ilara Mokin.
- ★ Obtained distinctions in: Digital Systems, Computational Software, Object Oriented Programming and Design from Elizade University.

REFRENCES

Available upon request.